[logo chimes]
[wind blowing]
[birds singing]
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
- [Travis] Hey,
what are you doing?
- Hey, baby. How far are you?
- [Travis] About
15 minutes away.
I just wanna...
I might have to ask you have you
still got that video we made?
You know that one, wow.
- Yes, [laughs] yes.
I will dig it up.
Just hurry.
- [Travis] Oh you
miss me, do you?
- Because I can't
wait to see you.
- [Travis] I know you do.
- I need to see you, okay?
- [Travis] I need
to see you too.
- Okay, bye.
- [Travis] See ya, darling, bye.
[tapes rattling]
[machine whirs]
[tape crackles]
[sexy music plays]
[tense music]
[floorboards creaking]
[tense music continues]
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
Hello?
- [Mom] Hello darling, hello.
- Hi, mom.
- [Mom] [indistinct]
- No, it's just me.
- [Mom] I miss you
so much darling.
- I miss you too.
- [Mom] Be careful
there's a man out there
- Yeah, I heard about that.
Sick fuck!
Probably impotent
with mommy issues.
- [Mom] Are you being
careful, Ilith?
- I'm being careful.
- [Mom] I want you
to be careful.
- Yeah. I gotta go.
Travis is here.
Travis!
- [Mom] What's that
playing in the background?
- No, nothing,
nothing, it's just TV.
- [Mom] Oh no, darling.
Are you still with him?
- Yeah, we're back together.
- [Mom] Oh god,
he's a little boy.
- Well, you don't know
him the way that I do.
- [Mom] Oh no, I don't like him.
- Okay, I gotta go.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Okay, okay.
- Bye, bye.
- [Mom] Bye, bye.
[receiver clatters]
[sexy music continues on TV]
[tense music]
[tense music continues]
- Fucking hell.
Where did you come from?
Travis,
is that you?
Travis.
[chuckles]
Like to watch?
I'll give you something to
watch, you sick bastard!
You and that fucking camera.
And what the fuck
are you wearing?
[moaning]
Not so rough, baby.
Whoa!
[phone ringing]
[answerphone beeps]
- [Travis] Hey, babe, look,
I'm about 15 minutes away.
I have to go back because
they screwed up my pizza order.
I asked for...
[screams]
[tense music]
[she screams]
[blows landing]
[party blower squeaks]
[confetti cannons pop]
[girls giggling]
[girls laughing]
[all scream]
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
[phone ringing]
[bell tolls]
- [Victoria] Hello?
- [Trevor] Hello,
is Victoria Benora there?
- [Victoria] It's
Miss Victoria, dear.
- [Trevor] My name is Trevor
Bates from Coogee, First Nationa
- [Victoria] Yes?
- [Trevor] I'm from your bank,
Miss Victoria.
I'm just following up on the
letter we sent you last week
regarding the
arrears on your loan.
Your mortgage?
Miss Victoria, do you remember
receiving that letter?
- [Victoria] I'm very busy.
What is it I can
do for you today?
- [Trevor] Miss Victoria,
you are over 120 days behind.
You haven't contacted us
regarding a payment plan.
You're leaving us no
option but to foreclose.
- [Victoria] You're
not taking my house.
- I will never...
- Victoria.
- [Trevor] Victoria, please.
- [Victoria] I've lived
here over 40 years.
Do you think for a
minute that I'm going to just
walk out of here,
leave my family?
- [Trevor] I understand
the situation that you're in,
but it says here on your file
you used to rent out rooms
to university students.
That could be a viable option to
get you out of this situation.
- [Victoria] No, I am
not doing that again.
- [Trevor] Be that as it may,
we need this account brought up
to date by the end of the month.
[tense music]
- Hi, Victoria.
Yes.
I've picked up the
first two girls and, um.
Yeah, I'm on my way
to the train station
to pick up the final girl now.
Yeah, okay.
Sure. Okay. On my way.
[train rumbling]
[upbeat electronic music]
[upbeat electronic music
continues]
[music fades]
- I guess it's home for the
next three years at least.
- [Emilie] Yeah, well, it's
close to the uni and the beach,
and that's all I care about.
Oh, and the boys,
the boys on the beach.
- What the hell
took you so long?
I've been waiting for hours.
You're all so inconsiderate,
making me wait in the
sun for you like this.
- I'll grab that.
- I've had every townie loser
hitting on me, it was repulsive.
I've never felt so violated.
- Hello.
- What's that?
Now you're checking me out.
Great. Well, that's all I need,
a lesbian drooling over me.
Thanks.
Now, if you can't
control your girlfriend,
then she can't live with this.
- You guys should just fuck.
And end it.
- I would film that for sure!
- Yeah, we'll put
it online, baby.
[eerie music]
[doorbell rings]
[door opens]
- You're late, Alex.
I said 9 a.m.
We're already halfway
through the morning.
- Sorry, Miss Victoria.
- Just take the bags upstairs.
- I'm gonna go down for a little
swim if you ladies want to join?
- Thank you, boys.
Now,
I don't know how you
girls do things back...
wherever it is you're from,
but here we're brought
up to respect our
elders and authority.
And as you're now
living under my roof,
[door slams]
you will obey my rules.
Bedrooms and bathrooms
are upstairs.
No boys in bedrooms ever.
Keep your rooms clean.
Do your own laundry and
make your own meals.
And under no circumstances
do you break any of my rules.
Remember, this is
still my house.
- You must be Victoria.
- Miss Victoria, dear.
You will call me Miss Victoria.
Any questions?
Good, Gwen will show
you to your rooms.
- Right away, Miss Victoria.
- What's her problem?
- No, boys?
What's all this about rules?
I didn't choose this university
because of its reputation
or academic standing.
I chose it because it's
3000 miles from my parents.
Now I'm stuck here with you.
And you.
- I'm sure she's
being dramatic, right?
I don't need to be
told how to behave
if I want to have a
three-way around the world
with the local football team.
I'm gonna.
- Hey, what happened
to you as a child?
- No boys in bedrooms,
no guests after 8 p.m.
No eating in bedrooms,
no alcohol or drugs.
What the fuck?
This is a fucking convent.
- No wine?
And how am I supposed to study?
- She can't be serious.
- She is serious.
I got the same talk last week,
and she does enforce the rules.
Kind of cute, in a way.
I'm Nola.
We're new roommates.
- Hello. I'm Emilie Charpentier.
- Satoshi Nara.
- Satoshi? Cool name.
- I'm Aspen Mason.
What do you mean, she's serious?
It's not the Middle Ages.
- The good news is we get
an Australia Day party.
-m Australia Day?
- Sounds made up.
- Made up?
You must be top of the class.
It's the last long weekend for
the start of the academic year.
It should be a blast.
- What about porn?
- Porn?
- Yeah, porn.
Are there rules about that?
- Please keep your voice down.
- That's something you'll have
to take up with Miss Victoria.
[playful music]
- Oh, Victoria, you
know you want it.
- [Nola] Ah, she will hear you.
- Wait, wait, wait, right there.
- Take it.
- Okay, okay, better stop
before she picks up on it.
- Oh, look at Nola, not liking
the girl-on-girl action.
Thought that would be right up
your alley, being from New York.
[basketball thuds]
- Didn't catch your name.
- It's Abigail.
Abigail Mason.
- Sisters?
- Yeah, right.
Daddy loves his business trips.
- So it's just us
that live here?
- [Nola] Us and Dr B.
- Doctor B?
- Dr Braun is the head of
the chemistry department.
You have heard of chemistry?
You can thank her for
the Australia Day party.
- Sounds like a blast.
- Abigail, let's unpack later.
I want to hit the beach.
I could do with a coffee,
though, that she was here.
- Just grabbing my phone.
[footsteps tapping]
[tense music]
- My dear.
- Yes, Miss Victoria.
- If you're joining them, be a
pet and bring back some milk.
- Will do, Victoria.
- Miss Victoria, dear.
- Um, Miss Victoria,
how do I look?
I mean, I feel
really fat, and...
- Gwendolyn just run along
and get something to eat.
Gwen.
- Yes?
- Milk.
- Okay.
[upbeat electronic music]
[upbeat electronic music
continues]
[waves crashing]
- I love the sea,
the water's so liberating.
So strong, yet helpless
at the same time.
[indistinct]
Just amazing.
[waves crashing]
Their dominance.
The unforgiving nature.
Relentless.
Truly biblical.
We don't have anything like
this back where I'm from.
The best we have is
a mermaid waterhole
that's dry six months a year.
- Dry holes.
Bummer.
[eerie music]
[waves crashing]
[ethereal music]
- You must be Abigail.
Well, take a seat,
I'm Doctor Braun.
All the way from
Broken Hill, I hear.
It must be a bit
of a shock to you.
All of this?
[chuckles]
Mm.
Such a big city like Sydney.
All the excitement.
All the boys.
Make a little girl's head spin.
[sighs]
[sniffs]
- Aspen.
- Aspen, you know
how flexible I am.
Flexibility is the
key to happiness.
I know you like flexible.
I can teach.
Jesus. What the...
- Just move.
- Victoria isn't going
to be putting up with
anybody getting into..
- Getting what?
- Just saying.
[eerie music]
- Careful, my little croissant.
She needs to be taught a lesson.
Doesn't know who
she's dealing with at.
[speaks French]
[gentle music]
I love the ballet.
Makes me feel like I'm
the only one in the world.
It's so involved that
I don't notice the time
and what's going on around me.
Only the music.
And my body.
It's like I'm on my
own little planet.
It's like making love.
[gentle music continues]
To a woman, you know?
Oh, no you wouldn't.
I'm concentrating on
studying this here, but I
want to stay in shape.
I'm happy to teach
you some positions.
You have the body
of a ballerina.
Well, kind of.
We can work on it.
[eerie music]
[birds chirping]
- When was the last
time you saw dad?
I haven't seen him in months.
He's probably out starting
a family somewhere.
Who knows?
We may have another sister.
[gentle music]
[shovel scraping]
- What's with the whole
new talking thing?
- Look at his back.
I love a man with a strong back.
- She's mute, I guess.
- Yeah. Strong back.
Yum.
And those arms.
- I'm more drawn to the abs.
The better the abs,
the better the pounding.
I once had a 12-pack.
I heard she walked in on
her mother hanging herself.
She was eight years
old, it fucked with her head
like it would anyone.
- That's so sad.
- Wait. 12 pack.
How can a guy have a 12 pack?
- Who said one guy.
I'm talking three way, baby.
They fucking knocked
the back out of me.
[chuckling]
- Ladies...
I trust we're all behaving
like young ladies.
- [All] Yes.
- Well, well, well, Dr B
going for the help.
- I think it's cute.
- Hi, my name's Ricky.
I can't spell my own name,
but I've got a big dick.
Do you want to suck it?
- Mmm, big dick?
Why, that's my
favourite kind of dick.
But how will I fit it all in?
- Yeah, lucky I have two hands.
- Two hands?
Nola, what the fuck is that?
- Is this so you talk dirty?
Two hands? [laughs]
- Yeah, two hands so I can
stick them up your ass.
[they laugh]
- Looking great, as always.
How do you do it?
- I was gonna ask you
the exact same thing.
- Oh.
- Wow, you're sweating so much.
Can I get you a drink?
Looks like you could use one.
- That'd be great, yeah.
Anything cold, thanks.
Oh, damn, it's hot.
- It certainly is.
- Mhm.
[she laughs]
- Hey, I started reading
that book you gave me,
but I don't get it.
I mean, where's the problem?
Braddock, that's
his name, right.
So
if he's shagging the girl and
the mother, where's the problem?
- Ricky, have you
actually read the book?
- Yeah, I've read the start.
- Well, until you do,
I think you should...
Actually, I've got the
DVD back at my place.
I mean, we could watch it
this afternoon if you're free.
- DVD?
You mean it's a movie?
So why would you give
me a book to read?
- I guess I thought you
might enjoy the read.
Clearly, I was wrong.
So how about it?
- I could either continue
reading this book at my own pace
and most likely finished
by Easter, if not longer,
or kick back and enjoy a
movie for a couple of hours
and enjoy some popcorn
and have a few beers.
- Mm, let me get you that drink.
- Mm.
[electronic music]
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Just getting this.
- Think the boys will
like what they see?
- You're not going
around dressed like that?
- Of course not.
Can't have Queen
Gertrude disapproving of my
choice of outfit.
- I love your confidence.
You're a model, you've got all
the confidence in the world.
You see what you
like and you take it.
Guys must love that.
Almost primal in a way.
Something I don't
think I could ever do.
[tense music]
- Funny.
Hey, um, can you use the
other side of the bed?
That one doesn't squeak.
- Are you planning on
having the guys up here
for a personal party?
- Honey, all I have to
do is lay down and the party
will come on...to me.
- So wrong.
[footsteps tapping]
- You're funny.
[dance music plays]
[indistinct chatter]
[dance music continues]
[glasses clink]
- Come on, baby, work for me.
Do something for me.
Come on.
Oh, don't be like this.
Come on, baby.
You know how I could use you.
The projector's fucked.
Fucking hell.
Well, hello, little lady.
We have a no love on
the projector front.
No, it's fucked, I've tried
for, like, half an hour.
I don't know it's this fucking
Bluetooth or something.
It doesn't need that,
it doesn't need cables.
[button clicks]
I'll be blind.
Nice work.
Blu-ray.
Yeah, cheers, good job.
I fixed the projector, everyone.
- Guys, do you reckon
the old lady will let
us stay past 10 p.m.?
[laughs]
Hmm?
- Got an invite, right?
[confetti cannon pops] Whoa!
- Yeah, I did.
Got an invite for a, uh,
a party.
Oh, Oh my God.
- Yeah. [high fives]
- Yeah.
- Such a sleaze.
- That's right.
- Blue ball, middle pocket.
[they laugh]
- Oh, mate, look at that arse.
It's just mesmerizing.
I want to go down there,
and I want to be consumed by it.
- Yeah.
- Like a giant human butt plug,
like,
[makes popping sound]
- Consumed? Fuck that man.
If I go down there,
I'm never coming back.
I'm just like, humana,
humana, humana.
Know what I mean?
I just want to set
up camp down there
and just become one with
my surroundings, you know?
Everyone will be like,
where the fuck is James?
You just tell 'em I'm
down there camping.
I'm getting one with nature.
- Yeah.
- Guys, who's going camping?
- Oh, hey.
More like pitching a tent.
[they laugh]
- We were talking about
the history of this place.
- Um, architecture?
- Yeah, yeah, the architecture.
There's a story I
want to tell you.
Have you heard the
story of the house?
- No.
- Girls, have you heard
the story of the house?
It's pretty hectic, come.
- Um, yeah.
So there's a story
about the house.
Come, I'll show you.
[fire roaring]
- Um, do you guys know that
Victoria had a daughter?
Shaking your head, man,
why are you shaking your head?
- I just don't think you
should be telling them.
- The girls live in the house,
they have a right to know.
- All right.
Okay.
[eerie music]
- 20 years ago in this house,
Victoria's daughter was home
one night, studying alone
when she was confronted
by an intruder
with only one thing on his mind.
She did all she could to
stop him and get away.
But he was too strong.
Holding her down,
raping and beating her within
an inch of her life.
Little did she know,
the horror had just begun.
Victoria, nursing her
through the pain,
helped deliver the baby.
Crazed with the pain of it all,
she smothers the baby,
then hangs herself.
They say the baby didn't die.
They...
They think he's still out there.
They think that he's
wandering the neighbourhood
looking for revenge.
Looking for blood.
- Bullshit.
There would be proof, right?
- Yeah, I know, right?
- Not like people
just disappear.
- Ah!
[clears throat]
- Hey, doc.
- Doc made it.
- Doc is in the house.
[balloon gushes]
[Alex laughs]
- [Doc] Having fun, children?
- Uh-huh.
- I am now.
- We are now.
[party music on background]
- Yeah.
A little bit hot for you, Nola?
- I like frankfurts.
- [James] Oh.
- Oh, you really have never had
a dick in your mouth before,
have you ever?
- I just like frankfurts.
- Oh. Oh, my God, is she frigid?
Oh, honestly, a true
blue cherry popping.
- All right, all right.
- Christ, now I know how
to deal with virgins.
Okay, you put down a tarp.
[laughter]
Just a joke, sorry.
Yeah, it was a joke.
Nola, come on.
[All] Come on Nola!
Come on!
Oh, that was good.
Oh, talking about Abigail.
Fucking hell, looking like that,
not being able to talk.
I don't care, throw
in a blowjob, she's
the perfect woman.
- Mm-hm.
- Fuck, yeah!
- What an asshole.
Such a fucking tool.
Me being a virgin and
that bullshit story.
- Do you think it's true?
- What?
- Well, hey, look who
finally found her voice.
I knew she could talk.
Guys! Come on.
I just want to get my
degree and get out of here.
But look, if this place
is too much for you,
we could probably all find
accommodation together.
- What about us?
Right? We're already here.
You think we don't
want the Hilton?
- Fine.
The story kind of spooked
me out a little, too.
But you're right,
it's got to be bullshit.
That guy doesn't know
what he's talking about.
If you guys just want
to stand around frowning
about it all night,
that's fine, but I'm out.
I'm gonna go have fun.
[eerie music]
[music intensifies]
- What do you
think you're doing?
- I'm just checking out if
there's another bathroom,
one that's more of a private
enterprise, you know?
I'm not a fan of the
communal lavatory.
I don't like the idea
that everyone has the equal
right to share their
filth in the same place.
I mean, you like
your privacy, right?
- Your bathrooms are upstairs.
[tense music]
[door creaks]
[suspenseful music]
Hi, how are you?
Victoria.
So this is your
dirty little secret.
[suspenseful music continues]
[whip cracks]
What's this?
Heavy duty.
[suspenseful music continues]
[groaning]
[body thuds]
[suspenseful music continues]
- We should leave.
And find a new place.
- What?
- She wants to leave.
- You can talk.
- Yeah.
[James laughs]
- Guys, this beats
paying a fortune
for a girls dorm that's
just full of girls.
You know what that means?
It's good for Emile,
but not for me.
- I like the peace and quiet.
Yeah,
girls dorm sounds like
cool enough for me.
If we're having a
vote, I vote dorms.
- Oh, I'm not going anywhere.
- Are we all missing the
fact that she just spoke?
- I don't know what
all the fuss is about.
I'm not going anywhere.
But if you want to leave.
No one's stopping you.
- Where's Aspen?
America. Mm.
[door rattling]
[glass clinks]
[liquid sploshing]
- Well, you've
successfully freaked everyone
out about the house.
I'm sure they're about somewhere
looking for ghosts.
[door creaks]
- Ah!
[Doc gasps]
- Gotcha!
- Oh my God!
Calm down tiger!
[moaning]
- Oh, fuck me, you
are a sexy thing.
- You're a bad little caveman,
aren't you?
Yes. Oh!
[Doc laughs]
[moaning]
[laughing]
Okay, calm down, tiger.
What about the DVD?
- DVD?
- Don't be a stud.
- I think this is crazy.
- Aspen's phone number?
- Why?
Why would you need to call her?
I think you're blowing
this way out of proportion.
[suspenseful music]
Is it true what they
say about your mom?
Look, I understand if you
don't want to talk about it.
I just realise how hard
it would have been.
Did you think of going and
live with your dad in Aspen?
[Doc moaning]
- Oh.
Just wait, just
wait, wait, wait.
- What?
- DVD.
[door rattles and opens]
- Yes?
- Hey, doc.
Sorry to disturb you.
Can we please grab Aspen's
phone number off you?
- Sure.
- Abigail just wants to
make sure she's okay.
- Okay. Just one sec.
- So I guess we're not
going to talk about it.
[upbeat music]
[water splashes]
- 0417...
- Uh, we don't have...
- Just use mine.
[phone vibrating]
- Straight to voicemail.
- [Voicemail] The mobile number
you are calling
is not responding.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
[voicemail beeps]
- Well, that didn't
solve a thing.
What now, genius?
[floorboards creaking]
[tense music]
[tense music continues]
[upbeat music]
[ballet music plays]
[record scratches]
[record crackles softly]
[music begins again]
[record scratches]
[speaking French]
[record crackles softly]
[music begins again]
[dramatic orchestral music]
[blade slashes]
[dramatic orchestral finish]
[flesh squelching]
[body thuds]
[tense music]
- Look, if you're so convinced
that shit's gone bad,
then just call the cops.
- Cops? Come on, girls,
are you serious?
- Christ, it's a party
and you want to call the cops?
For what?
Because one girl's gone missing,
or you think has gone missing.
- Guys, what's going on?
- Abigail wants
to call the cops.
- Troopers?
Bring it on,
I haven't been frisked in weeks.
- Not stripping type.
She wants the party's
over, you have the right to
remain silent, type.
- Ah, you've gotta be kidding.
I liked it more when
she couldn't talk.
- Satoshi!
- What? If you're gonna call the
cops, get the stripping kind.
- Okay, look, just leave
the cops out of it and
calm the hell down, okay?
You're creating an
unnecessary panic.
We'll help you look.
Keeps you quiet.
Okay?
- So no handjob?
- James is at the pool.
I've been eyeballing
him from the window.
- I knew there was a handjob.
- No, not giving handjobs.
He... not giving
hand jobs, Satoshi.
- Emilie doesn't give handjobs,
she's more of a rug muncher.
[chuckling]
[reggae music plays]
[upbeat electronic music plays]
- Hey, where is Aspen and Emily?
I think Aspen has fallen
for Emilies charm.
There's a bit of an
oyster fest going on in the
bush if you ask me.
- James, get a new theme.
- Hi, uh, I'm wanting to report
possibly two missing persons.
- Over-fucking reaction.
- You guys should
consider yourself lucky.
Thanks to Dr B, Victoria, let us
have this little get together.
Here we are calling the cops.
Just the kind of attention
she doesn't want.
- Come on, guys, this is stupid.
It's a party, right?
Let's have some fun.
- Seriously, this
is an absolute joke.
Ricky and I gonna go watch a DVD
and you guys can hang around and
play Scooby gang all you like.
- All right, yeah, look, we'll
help if that'll shut you up.
And mean that we can
get back to the party, have
a couple of drinks.
- I'll go check out the pool.
- Yeah, sure, we'll
look around here.
- Shit, I'm impressed that you
could resist me for so long.
- Just shut up.
- Oh! Jesus.
God, you are smoking.
What the hell?
Hey! You naughty little nun.
Oh!
- Have you ever had acupuncture?
- Yeah.
- Anyway.
If I do this right, I'm gonna
have you orgasming for an hour.
- Really?
Where are you putting that?
- You need to stay really still.
- No, no,
Whoa. Oh my God.
No, no, no, don't.
Oh! My god.
Oh. Have you done this before?
- I have done this a
lot of times before.
- [James] Oh my God.
Oh, that's really good.
- You're not going in there.
[tense music]
[door closes]
[projector whirs]
[moaning and screaming]
[screaming]
- Kill that fucker.
[objects clattering]
[extinguisher hissing]
[hatch opens]
[light switch clicks]
[static hissing]
[video recorder whirring]
[tense music]
[extinguisher hissing]
- How dare you!
Give me that!
Give that to me!
You don't know
what you're doing!
She's just a beautiful,
young, innocent girl.
And she's just like my daughter.
She is my daughter.
Ow! ow!
[Victoria screams]
Oh!
[tense music continues]
[combatants grunting]
[moaning]
Oh! Oh Ricky!
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
what was that?
- It's the movie.
Focus on me.
I thought we were gonna
watch a movie first.
- Maybe this is the movie.
[chuckles]
So cute but so dumb.
[moaning]
[slapping]
[Doc shrieks]
[moaning]
[tense music continues]
[combatants grunting]
- Just making sure
you don't go anywhere.
I'll deal with you later.
[suspenseful music]
[tense music]
- Oh, don't stop, don't stop.
- I heard something.
- Yeah, it was me moaning.
You were sticking
needles into my nuts.
[outside scream]
Oh, that is the most
fake scream ever.
- And what makes
you such an expert?
- Believe it or not, I've
got a couple of fake screams
before in my time.
[eerie music]
[tense music]
[Nola gasping]
[Nola gurgling]
[tense music continues]
Oh, yeah.
Oh that's fucking good.
Oh!
[door creaks]
[tense music]
Ah yeah.
Oh.
[dramatic music]
[blade slashes]
[James screaming]
[blade swishes]
[eerie music]
[bright guitar music]
- Alex, I know it's you.
I can smell erectile
dysfunction from a mile away.
Shouldn't you be looking
for your friends?
Move.
Move!
Wait.
Leave me alone!
[music continues]
[water splashes]
[water splashing]
[flesh squelches]
[music continues]
[lock rattling]
[eerie music]
- Oh fuck!
[gasping] Yes! Yes!
[extinguisher clangs]
[both moaning]
- Oh, yes.
- Whoo!
Oh, baby.
[hand slaps]
[moaning]
- Animal! Yes!
Fuck me! Oh, God.
[moaning]
[tense music]
Fuck! Yes!
Oh, God!
[screaming]
Oh God, Ricky!
[moaning]
[blow lands]
- Oh fuck!
[Doc screams]
[chainsaw buzzes]
[Doc screaming]
[tense music continues]
[eerie music]
[grunts]
[objects clatter]
[chainsaw buzzing]
- Stop!
Please stop.
Don't you understand?
He's gone.
Gone.
[chainsaw buzzing]
[body thuds]
[screaming]
[tense music]
[gasping]
[chainsaw buzzing]
[screaming]
[grunting]
[suspenseful music]
[sobbing]
[chainsaw buzzing]
[water splashing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[chainsaw buzzing]
[body thuds]
[wipers swishing]
[dramatic music]
[chainsaw buzzing]
[choking]
[music intensifies]
[bottle smashes]
[tense music]
[grunting]
[chainsaw buzzing]
[screams]
[flames roaring]
[suspenseful music]
[tense music]
[tense music continues]